A Guide to Records of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1995-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1995-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)
The Library of Virginia
44684
100.5 cu. ft. (104 boxes)
Virginia Secretary of Commerce and Trade
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected and confidential information is restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78, 2.2-3800, and 2.2-3705.1-8. Restricted documents have been sealed within the collection.
Acquisition Information
Transferred by the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 2010.
Historical Information
In 1970, the Governor's Management Commission Study recommended the creation of six 'Deputy Governors' to assist the Chief Executive in his managerial duties, compatible functions of government were grouped under these administrative heads, who would serve as the Governors top management team or "secretariats," as they are called now. The General Assembly in 1972 created six Secretariats positions initially. As government reorganized, that number fluctuated when government agencies expanded or consolidated.
The office of the Secretary of Commerce and Resources was established in 1972 and was responsible for the areas of economic development and natural resources. In 1986 this secretariat was dissolved and split into two separate offices, the Secretary of Economic Development and the Secretary of Natural Resources. In 1993 the name of the office was changed from the Secretary of Economic Development to the Secretary of Commerce and Trade. Patrick O. Gottschalk served as Secretary of Commerce and Trade during Governor Timothy M. Kaine's administration (2006-2010).
The Secretary of Commerce and Trade is appointed by the governor and serves as a member of his cabinet. The Secretary of Commerce and Trade's chief responsibility is to manage the direction of several state agencies that are concerned with the development of commerce and economic development throughout the Commonwealth. Some of the agencies reporting to the Secretary of Commerce and Trade include: Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services; Department of Economic Development; Department of Labor and Industry; Department of Mines, Minerals, and Energy; Virginia Employment Commission; Virginia Housing Development Authority; Department of Professional and Occupational Regulations; Department of Housing and Community Development; Milk Commission; Department of Minority Business Enterprise; Department of Forestry; Virginia Port Authority; Virginia Racing Commission; and Virginia Resource Authority.
Scope and Content
Records of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 2006-2010, during the administration of Governor Timothy Kaine. The collection is housed in 104 boxes and includes agendas, briefings, brochures, clippings, contracts, correspondence, financial statements, itineraries, maps, memorandum, newsletters, notes, photographs, programs, publications, reports, and other documents.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Constituent Correspondence
Series II: Governor's Opportunity Fund Files
Series III: Agency Correspondence
Series IV: Special Projects and Studies
Series V: Public Relations, Activities, and Events
Series VI: Development Projects and Initiatives
Series VII: Secretary's Correspondence
Series VIII: Files
Series IX: Economic Development Organizations
Series X: Warner Administration Records.
Contents List
- Series I: Constituent Correspondence, 2006-2009., Extent: 14 boxes. (Box 1-13, 104)
  - Constituent Correspondence, Jan.-June 2006. (Box 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, July-Dec. 2006. (Box 2)
  - Constituent Correspondence, Jan.-May 2007. (Box 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, May-Oct. 2007. (Box 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, Oct. 2007-Feb. 2008. (Box 5)
  - Constituent Correspondence, Feb.-June 2008. (Box 6)
  - Constituent Correspondence, June-Sep. 2008. (Box 7)
  - Constituent Correspondence, Sep. 2008-Jan. 2009. (Box 8)
  - Constituent Correspondence, Jan.-Mar. 2009. (Box 9)
  - Constituent Correspondence, Mar.-May 2009. (Box 10)
  - Constituent Correspondence, May-Aug. 2009. (Box 11)
  - Constituent Correspondence, Aug.-Nov. 2009. (Box 12)
  - Constituent Correspondence, Nov.-Dec. 2009. (Box 13)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2006-2010. (Box 104)
- Series II: Governor's Opportunity Fund Files, 2006-2009., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 14-15)
  Governor's Opportunity Fund Files contains the records of the Virginia Economic Development Partnership (VEDP), specifically for the Governor's Opportunity Fund (GOF), a "deal closing" fund to be employed at the Governor's discretion when necessary to secure a company location or expansion in Virginia and for the Virginia Investment Performance Grant (VIP), which encourages continued capital investment by existing Virginia companies. The files are organized alphabetically by company name.
  - VEDP GOF/VIP Projects--Active, A-W. (Box 14, Folder 1-83)
  - GOF/VIP Completed, A-D. (Box 14, Folder 84-110)
  - GOF/VIP Completed, D-W. (Box 15, Folder 1-78)
- Series III: Agency Correspondence, 2006-2009., Extent: 25 boxes. (Box 16-40)
  Agency Correspondence contains the correspondnece and other records of various agencies under the Secretary of Commerce and Trade. These include the Virginia Employment Commission (VEC); Virginia Tourism Corporation (VTC); Board of Accountancy (BOA); Department of Business Assistance (DBA); Department of Housing and Community Development (DHCD); Virginia Resources Authority (VRA); Department of Labor and Industry (DOLI); Department of Professional and Occupational Regulation (DPOR); the Virginia Racing Commission (VRC); Department of Mines, Minerals, and Energy (DMME); Virginia Housing Development Authority (VHDA); Virginia Tobacco Commission (VTIC); and Virginia Ecnomic Development Partnership (VEDP).
  - VEC (Box 16)
  - VEC (Box 16)
  - VEC (Box 16)
  - VEC Board Meetings. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - VEC VA Business Resource Directory. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - VEC Congressional Meetings, Apr. 24, 2008. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - VEC Constituent Correspondence. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - VEC Continuity of Operations Plan (COOP). (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - VEC U.S. Department of Labor. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - VEC U.S. Department of Labor (Agreement Between Commonwealth of VA and US Dept of Labor). (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - VEC Executive Order 19--Serving Virginia's Veterans. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - VEC Expense Reports. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - VEC Extended Benefits Agreement. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - VEC Financial Statements. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - VEC Financing Shorfall. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - VEC General Correspondence. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - VEC H-2B. (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - VEC Immigration. (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - VEC Memorandum of Understanding (Executive Order #25). (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - VEC Plan for Expenditure of Fiscal Year. (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - VEC Pay Card. (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - VEC Printing Authorizations. (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - VEC Smithfield Foods, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - VEC Southside Economic Development Project. (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - VEC State Plan Requests. (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - VEC UI Compensation. (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - VEC Unemployment Compensation Trust Fund. (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - VEC Unemployment Compensation. (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - VEC Vaughan Furniture Galax County. (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - VEC VCU Occupational Safety and Health Compliance Officer Study. (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - VEC VITA. (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - VEC VWNIS. (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - VEC VWNIS Replacement Project Plan. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - VEC Wagner-Peyser Act. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - VEC Workforce. (Box 17, Folder 3-10)
  - VEC Workforce Investment Act (WIA). (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - VEC Workforce Investment Boards (WIB). (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - VEC Reduction of Workforce Letter to Legislators. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - VEC Work Opportunity Tax Credit (WOTC). (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - VEC Yorktowne Cabinetry. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - VTC Advantus Strategies, LLC (Virginia Film Incentives). (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - VTC Air Service Industry Briefing. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - VTC "Big Stone Gap" Movie. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - VTC Blue Ridge Parkway. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - VTC Board Meetings. (Box 18, Folder 5-12)
  - VTC Chakravarty Cup-Polo. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - VTC Constituent Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - VTC Continuity of Operations Plan (COOP). (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - VTC Dashboard Newsletter. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - VTC Tourism Development Report. (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - VTC Economic Impact Figures, 2007. (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - VTC Executive Order Requests. (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - VTC Expense Reports. (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - VTC Film Projects (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - VTC Virginia Tourism Corp. Agency Correspondence. (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - VTC Financial Stability. (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - VTC General Correspondence. (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
  - VTC Governor's Motion Opportunity Fund (GMPOF). (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - VTC Henrico County Open Golf Tournament. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - VTC Highway Information Media. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - VTC Jamestown 2007. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - VTC John Adams Reception and Premier Screening. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - VTC National Organization of Black Law Enforcement Executives (NOBLE). (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - VTC Live Passionately Campaign. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - VTC Poplar Hill Development. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - VTC Rest Area Closures. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - VTC U.S. Open Cycling Championships, 2007. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - VTC Virginia Chamber of Commerce (Tourism Paper). (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - VTC "Virginia is for Lovers" (VIFL) Infringement. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - VTC Western Hemisphere Travel Initiative. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - VTC Wine-Premier Pacific. (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - BOA Board Meetings. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - BOA Constituent Correspondence. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - BOA Executive Director (Wade A. Jewell). (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - BOA Financial Statements. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - BOA General Correspondence. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Department of Business Assistance. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - DBA Administration Division Reorganization. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - DBA Board Meetings. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - DBA Constituent Correspondence. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - DBA Continuity of Operations Plan (COOP). (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - DBA Expense Reports. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - DBA Financial Statements. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - DBA Financial Statements (VSBFA). (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - DBA General Correspondence. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - DBA General Issues. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - DBA Incumbent Worker. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - DBA Northrup Grumman/CGI-AMS. (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - DBA Printing Authorizations. (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - DBA Rowe Furniture. (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - DBA Small Business Advisory Board. (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - DBA Southwest Virginia Swing Trip (Business Appreciation Week). (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - DBA Sponsorship Requests. (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - DBA State Plane Requests. (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Southwest Virginia Strategic Task Force. (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - DBA SWaM. (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Commerce and Trade Procurement Fair-SWAM. (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - DBA Virginia Jobs Investment Program. (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - DBA VEDA Membership Dues for Secretary. (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - DBA VSBFA. (Box 20, Folder 29-31)
  - DBA VSBFA (Board Meetings). (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - DBA VSBFA (General Correspondence). (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - DBA VSBFA Audit. (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - DHCD Appalachian Regional Commission (ARC). (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
  - DHCD 2008 ARC Annual Strategy Statement. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - DHCD ARRA Administrative Overview. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - DHCD ARRA Broadband Application Consultant RFP. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - DHCD A&W Heritage Place (Prince Edward County). (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - DHCD Broadband Study for Hampton Roads. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - DHCD Community Development Bank. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - DHCD Constituent Correspondence. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - DHCD CDBG Construction Ready Water and Sewer Fund Award. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - DHCD Town of Exmore (Governor's Visit). (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - DHCD Enterprise Zone. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - DHCD Executive Order Requests. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - DHCD Financial Statements. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - DHCD Fiscal Stress Report. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - DHCD General Correspondence. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - DHCD Homeless Prevention and Rapid Re-Housing Program (HPRP). (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - DHCD MacArthur Foundation (Window of Opportunity Proposal). (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - DHCD Catalog of State and Local Mandates on Local Governments. (Box 22, Folder 1-5)
  - DHCD Plan for Expenditure of Fiscal Year. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - DHCD Printing Authorizations (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - DHCD Private Activity Bond Allocation. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - DHCD Schedule of Assessment Periods. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - DHCD Southern Rivers Watershed Enhancement Program Grant Awards. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - DHCD Space Planning/Move. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - DHCD Town of Tangier Funding. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - DHCD Taylor's Valley Community Club. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - DHCD CDBG (American Recovery and Reinvestment Act Funding). (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - DHCD VCDBG--VA Community Development Block Grant Program. (Box 22, Folder 15-16)
  - DHCD CDBG Recovery Funds (CDBG-R). (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - DHCD Virginia Community Capital (VCC) "Authorized Entity" for ARRA. (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - DHCD Virginia Enterprise Initiative. (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - DHCD Virginia Main Street (Design Contract RFP). (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - DHCD 2007 Virginia Main Street Communities. (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - DHCD Virginia Neighborhood Stabilization Program. (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - DHCD WHRO--Hampton Roads (Broadband). (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - VRA Board Meetings. (Box 23, Folder 1-6)
  - VRA Confidential Board Matters. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - VRA Broadband. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - VRA Constituent Correspondence. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - VRA Expense Reports. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - VRA Financial Statements. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - VRA Secretary of Commerce & Trade Meeting. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - VRA Energy Collaboration--VRA & DMME). (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - VRA General Correspondence. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - VRA Infrastructure Revenue Bonds. (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - VRA Southeastern Public Service Authority (SPSA). (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Department of Labor and Industry. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - DOLI Advanced Technologies, Inc. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - DOLI American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME). (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - DOLI Board Meetings. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - DOLI Child Labor Law Amendments. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - DOLI Communications Workers of America. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - DOLI Constituent Correspondence. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - DOLI Executive Orders. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - DOLI Expense Reports. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - DOLI Financial Statements. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - DOLI General Correspondence. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - DOLI House Bill 30/Senate Bill 30. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - DOLI International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW). (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - DOLI International Labor Organization (ILO). (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - DOLI Printing Authorizations. (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - DOLI The Study of Safety and Health Staffing for VOSH (Summary of VCU's Draft). (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - DOLI United Steel Workers Union. (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - DOLI Washington Gas/Shenandoah Gas. (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - DOPR Board Meetings. (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - DPOR Common Interest Community Board. (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - DPOR Complaints (DPOR Employees). (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - DPOR Constituent Correspondence. (Box 24, Folder 22-23)
  - DPOR Expense Reports. (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - DPOR Financial Statements. (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - DPOR General Correspondence. (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - DPOR McCatty, Earl v. DPOR. (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - DPOR NCEES Issue. (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - DPOR Printing Authorizations. (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - DPOR Report on Audit (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Virginia Racing Commission. (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - VRC Stanley Bowker. (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - VRC Expense Reports. (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - VRC Constituent Correspondence. (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - VRC Financial Statements. (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - VRC General Correspondence. (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - VRC Virginia Thoroughbred Association. (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - DMME Alternative Fuels. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - DMME Board Meetings. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - DMME Coal Mine Emergency Preparedness. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - DMME CNX Gas Company v. Jason Poulos, et al. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - DMME Constituent Correspondence (DGMR Budget Cuts 2008). (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - DMME Consolidation of Southwest Virginia Locations. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - DMME Director Appointment. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - DMME Elkton Energy Research Center. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - DMME U.S. Department of Energy Loan Guarantee Program. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - DMME Energy. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - DMME Department of Energy Small Business Innovation Research (SBIR) Program. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - DMME Expense Reports. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - DMME Financial Statements. (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - DMME GE Energy. (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - DMME General Correspondence. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - DMME GEOMET Operation Company, Inc. (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - DMME Global Energy Project Review. (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - DMME HB 1443 Assessment of the Availability of Effective Underground Wireless Comm. and Miner Locator Systems. (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Interstate Mining Compact Commission (IMCC). (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - DMME Interstate Oil Gas and Compact Commission (IOGCC). (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - DMME Kentucky AG. (Box 25, Folder 21.)
  - DMME Levisa Coal Company v. Consolidation Coal Company. (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - DMME Michael G. McGlothlin-Summons. (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - DMME Mine Rescue Teams. (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - DMME Mine Safety. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - DMME Mountaintop Mining. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - DMME Oil Overcharge Report. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - DMME Shell Oil. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - DMME Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS). (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - DMME Training Programs. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - DMME United Coal Company (UCC). (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - DMME Virginia Mining Journal. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - DMME Virginia Uranium, Inc. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - DMME George P. "Bo" Willis. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - VHDA Board Meetings. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - VHDA Capital Reserve Funds. (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - VHDA Constituent Correspondence. (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - VHDA Expense Reports. (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - VHDA Approval of Allocation Plan for Federal Low-Income Housing Tax Credits. (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - VHDA Executive Order #58. (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - VHDA Financial Statements. (Box 26, Folder 17-19)
  - VHDA General Correspondence. (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - VHDA Genesis Project Kickoff, Newport News. (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - VHDA Rental Housing Bonds. (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - VTIC Blue Ribbon Review Panel. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - VTIC Constituent Correspondence. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - VTIC Sanjay Dalmia Group. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - VTIC Education Committee Meetings. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - VTIC Enterprise Zone (EZ). (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - VTIC Executive Committee Meetings. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - VTIC Expense Reports (empty). (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - VTIC Financial Statements. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - VTIC Financial Statements (Virginia Tobacco Settlement Foundation). (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - VTIC General Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - VTIC The Institute for Advanced Learning and Research. (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - VTIC Long Range Plan Committee. (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - VTIC Neal Noyes. (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - VTIC Occupation and Education Gap Analyses. (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - VTIC Performance Agreements. (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - VTIC Ply Gem Windows. (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - VTIC Research & Development Committee. (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - VTIC State Plane Requests. (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - VTIC Technology Committee. (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - VTIC TROF/GOF Agreement (Sample). (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - VTIC Tobacco Region Opportunity Fund (Approvals). (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - VTIC Virginia Community Capital, Inc. (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - VTIC Workforce Development. (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - VTIC Blue Ribbon Commission Panel. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - VTIC Broadband. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - VTIC Carthan Currin. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - VTIC Board Meetings. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - VTIC Tobacco Commission Meetings. (Box 28, Folder 5-31)
  - VTIC Southside Economic Development Committee. (Box 29, Folder 1-8)
  - VTIC Special Projects Committee. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Economic Development Partnership. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - VEDP ABC Corp. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - VEDP Ace Building Systems. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - VEDP Advanced Auto Parts. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - VEDP Advertising. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - VEDP AGL/Giant LNG Joint Venture. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - VEDP Airline Industry. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - VEDP Alcoa Wheels. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - VEDP Alpha Natural Resources. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - VEDP Alston Power. (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - VEDP Altec USA, LLC. (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - VEDP AMD (Advanced Micro Devices). (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - VEDP American Industrial Heat Transfer. (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - VEDP AMIZ (Advanced Manufacturing Innovation Zone). (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - VEDP Jeffrey M. Anderson Executive Director. (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - VEDP APM Terminals North America. (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - VEDP Annual Report. (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - VEDP Project Anton International Strategy Corporation (ISC). (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - VEDP Applied Extrusion Technologies, Inc. (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - VEDP Apple (Project Core). (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - VEDP AREVA NP, Inc. (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - VEDP Arlington County. (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - VEDP Ashley Furniture. (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - VEDP Astra Zeneca Pharmaceuticals LP. (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - VEDP Australia. (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - VEDP Auto Industry. (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - VEDP AVRC (Advanced Vehicle Research Center). (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - VEDP BAE Defense Technology. (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - VEDP Base-X Expedition Systems. (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - VEDP BATSA (Business Activity Tax Simplification Act). (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - VEDP BaySys Technologies. (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - VEDP Blackwater USA. (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - VEDP Bluestone Regional Business and Technology Center. (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - VEDP Board Meetings. (Box 30, Folder 34-36)
  - VEDP BMW. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - VEDP Boehringer Ingelheim. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - VEDP Boy Scouts of America. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - VEDP BRAC. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - VEDP Bristol Compressor. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - VEDP Budget. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - VEDP Report on Business Incentives, 2005-2006. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - VEDP Economic Development Call Sheets. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - VEDP Canon Virginia, Inc. (Newport News). (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - VEDP Capital One. (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - VEDP Care Rehab and Orthopedic Products, Inc. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - VEDP Cary Street Partners/Alcoa Meeting. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - VEDP Cavco Industries, Inc. (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - VEDP CEO Dinners. (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - VEDP CGI. (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - VEDP Chile. (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - VEDP China. (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - VEDP Clarksville and Occoneechee State Park. (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - VEDP CNBC. (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - VEDP Coalfields Expressway. (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - VEDP Colt Defense LLC. (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - VEDP COM.40 Limited. (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - VEDP Commerce Quarterly. (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - VEDP ComTek (Communication Technologies). (Box 31, Folder 24)